Izumi!
Want these?
Accepted at Theaters Nationwide
Complimentary Ticket
Movie tickets?
Complimentary tickets.
I got them from a coworker of mine.
They're good until this Sunday.
And you're not going?
Can't. I've got work.
Take someone with you if you're free.
Later.
Thanks. Good luck at work.
Yep.
A movie...
Shikimori-san, do you like movies?
I do!
So tomorrow—
I'm free!
Okay, shall we go see a movie then?
I'd love to!
Shikimori's Not Just a Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not Just a Cutie
Amusement Park
Shikimori-san might like it??
Get a reservation!!!
Get gifts for the family
Eat this!!
Inuzuka-kun
Keep warm and go to bed early!!
Inuzuka-kun!!
Please Help
I'm going to an amusement park with
Shikimori-san next week. Suggestions...?
#03  Misfortune, Followed by Sunshine
I'm gonna see a movie
with Shikimori-san...
I can't wait!
No, no! I don't have time to just
sit around looking forward to it.
Whenever we've gone out together before...
The weather report would say it'd be sunny,
but then it'd suddenly start raining.
Or I'd drop my wallet and lose
a whole month's allowance.
Shikimori-san always just smiles
and acts like it's no big deal...
But I don't want her to suffer
because of my bad luck this time!
I've gotta prepare so I can handle
anything that might happen!
First, umbrellas.
I'll take a few in case
a sudden gust breaks one.
I'll put my wallet on a string
to make sure I don't drop it.
A towel in case we get splashed
with water or mud...
And this...
Oh, I'll bring a water bottle, too.
There!
I might've packed a little too much...
So... heavy...
Ack!
Ow, ow, ow...
That was a loud crash.
Yuu, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
"How to be a cute girl
without trying too hard..."
"Classic dresses that boyfriends love..."
"Look more girly with frills..."
"Your date outfit is your battle uniform"?!
What should I wear?
Hey, I'm coming in.
Could you keep it down?
I'm not making that much noise.
You going out somewhere?
Huh?
Uh, yeah... I'm going to the movies
tomorrow with... a friend.
What kind of friend?
I'm not telling you.
Harsh!
Well, good luck.
All right!
I can do this!
Okay! Today has started out
perfectly normally.
The strap on my bag snapped.
Then I found a lost child
and took her to the police.
But I left home early since I knew stuff
like that would happen, so we're good!
All right! I'm not late!
I won't have to make
Shikimori-san wait today.
Shikimori-san! There's still time
before we were supposed to meet...
Good morning, Izumi-san.
I'm sorry. I arrived a bit early.
Izumi-san? Do I look strange?
No, not strange...
You just look... really nice.
Thank you.
Shikimori-san is incredibly cute today!
This'll be our first time
seeing a movie together.
Ever since we left Toyko,
I've been in love with you.
I still am.
What if that actually happens?!
Izumi-san?
Huh?!
Your face is red. Do you have a fever?
I-I'm fine!
Are you sure?
I'm sure. I'm just too excited
to be seeing a movie with you.
I feel the same.
They've got a lot playing.
There are so many that it's hard to decide.
I wonder what genres Shikimori-san likes.
No matter what happens,
I'll keep my promise to you.
Weaving the future and the past
My heart is pounding...
What's happening to me?
Romance, maybe?
A Jelly Beans & Caramel Melon Production
Almond Schazganeyer in
JEANS OF SOUL
But she's really sporty, too.
Maybe she's into stuff like action.
Shikimori-san, which movie do you want to see?
Well, um... Anything's fine with me.
Whatever you want to see.
You know, you always say things like that.
Huh?
You always put where I want to go,
what I want to see, or what I want to eat first.
Do I really...?
You do!
Let's see the movie you want to see today!
Wh-Why?
"Why"?!
Y-Yes...
Because I want to know more about you!
Don't be shy. Just be frank with me.
Tell me the truth.
Which one do you want to see the most?
Um... well, then...
That one.
The Japanese Premiere
I opened the door and found
a smiling clown...
CAST
Ricky Churchill
Ship Johnston
Alexandra Toto
Shelley Rand
Adolf Yeltsin
Michael Chandler
H-Huh?
The Japanese Premiere
I opened the door and found
a smiling clown...
CAST
Ricky Churchill
Ship Johnston
Alexandra Toto
Shelley Rand
Adolf Yeltsin
Michael Chandler
Do you know this movie?
It's all the rage on social media.
I've been curious about it.
Oh, really?
Prepare to be traumatized!
Scariest movie I've seen all year
Nothing short of a masterpiece!
Must-see for horror fans
You're right. Sounds like it's super scary.
Oh, are you all right with horror movies?
Yeah, I guess I can handle them.
Oh, good!
Stuff like that doesn't scare you?
It does, but if it's scary,
I just can't help wanting to see it.
Oh, so she does get scared.
Damn it!
Stay away!
I'm okay with splatter films,
and I should be fine since we're in a theater.
Maybe...
Don't worry. I'm here for you.
Izumi-san!
Maybe I'll get to show
her how manly I can be!
Shikimori-san, tell me if you get scared.
I'm right here.
Okay. Thank you.
A balloon?
This is terrifying!
What the heck?! This is insanely scary!
Eurgh...
I'm so scared, I feel like I'm gonna puke...
Shikimori-san...
I-Izumi-san!
Are you all right, Izumi-san?
I didn't know you'd get this scared.
I'm so sorry. If I hadn't said
I wanted to see a horror movie...
I should be thanking you.
Huh?
If I'd been alone, I might've passed out.
Having you with me made me stronger.
I'm glad to hear that.
Shikimori-san, do you want
to go get something to eat?
I'd love to!
This looks so good! And cute!
It really is cute.
Walnut and Custard Cream Caramel
1,800 yen (with tax)
It's kind of expensive, though...
Don't worry! You can leave that to me!
I've been saving up in secret because
I wanted to try this with you.
Izumi-san...
Also, I just happen to have a coupon for...
Huh?
What's the matter?
What? My wallet's gone!
The coupon was in there.
No way... I put my wallet on a
string so I wouldn't lose it...
The string broke!
No way...
Tachikawa Station North Exit
Sorry, Shikimori-san.
It's all right. Please don't worry about it.
I really wanted to make you happy,
but it was all for nothing.
What? Yuu?
Huh? Mom and Dad?
What are you doing here?
Just a little shopping.
Nice to see you again, Shikimori-san.
H-Hello, Father and Mother!
"Mother," she says.
Mm-hm.
Are you on your way somewhere?
Well, we were going to get pancakes,
but I dropped my wallet.
Again, huh?
Same old story.
Y-Yeah...
Why don't you come eat at home, then?
If Shikimori-san comes with you,
we'll splurge on the snacks.
Oh, good idea! And I'll make us a feast.
What? But...
It would be my pleasure!
Eat all you like.
Thank you! I will!
I'll serve it up.
I-I can definitely see
the family resemblance.
Sorry, Shikimori-san!
You didn't hurt your hand, did you?
Are you okay?
I'm just fine.
This is delicious!
It tastes like something from a restaurant!
Go on. Eat your fill.
Thank you!
No need to be shy.
Okay!
Have some of this, too.
Oh, and this.
Sorry, Shikimori-san.
They're a little overexcited.
Not at all. I'm having a great time.
It's been a long time since
I had home cooking...
O-Oh, I didn't mean anything serious by that!
Shikimori-san.
You're welcome to visit our home
anytime you'd like.
We do tend to make too much food.
Okay.
I'll go get dessert ready.
Bathroom break for me.
Okay.
Thanks for coming over.
Sorry for putting you on the spot.
I'm glad I could come.
You don't seem nervous at all.
I totally panicked.
What are you talking about?
I'm in the home of the person I love.
Of course I'm nervous.
C-Could she be any cuter?!
Look at you, flirting in front of me.
I could weep tears of delight.
You're back?!
Allow me to help with the dishes.
Oh, are you sure?
You can just chat with Yuu if you want.
Well... Izumi-san fell asleep.
He's always been the type to fall
asleep once his belly's full.
Isn't that adorable?
Girlfriend brag?
Th-That's not what I meant!
I really would like to thank you.
For staying by his side.
Mother...
Is there anything you want to ask me
while we have this chance?
Like to see his middle school album,
or his baby pictures...
Huh?!
If not, then...
Could I ask you something?
You want to ask me something?
When he was in elementary school...
Yuu, listen to me.
Make sure you watch out for cars.
Always look up,
and mind where you step, too.
And don't forget to check
behind you as you walk.
Jeez, Mom, I'll be fine.
Just make sure you don't get hurt.
See you later!
He came home with new
injuries every single day.
I got so worried, I couldn't
send him off with a smile.
But you know, after sixteen years...
It wouldn't even faze me to suddenly
find a giant hole in the house.
A-Acclimation is an amazing thing...
It actually scares me.
Probably because he only ever
worries for other people,
and with the most oblivious look on his face.
What's wrong, Mom?
Your head...
Um, never mind...
Here.
Oh, dear. Thank you.
Honestly, where does he get it from?
It certainly is a mystery...
But that's why...
I just hope you won't
lose patience with him.
After all, I'm sure his bad luck
will cause you some hardship as well...
That's not true.
You're right that Izumi-san
runs into trouble quite often.
Maybe others see him as
unfortunate because of that.
But as for me...
I have never once thought of him that way.
His nature is not a flaw.
I think being so unlucky
is what makes him so kind.
Plus...
Izumi-san understands
pain better than anyone.
But in spite of that,
he never pities himself
and he's able to show concern for others.
Izumi-san san is so strong and admirable.
You don't need to worry.
I'll protect him.
Mother?
Oh, gosh... I'm starting to
wish you were my girlfriend.
Huh?!
Having an affair in front of me? I could cry.
Oh, you're here?
What?!
Yuu. Yuu, wake up.
It's already eight o'clock.
Mii-chan is going home.
What? It's already that late?
I need to walk her—
What are you two doing?
A gaming tournament!
Not bad, Mii-chan.
Same to you, Akisada-san.
They bonded before I even knew it.
Well, thank you for having me over.
Mii-chan...
Come over whenever you want, okay?
Okay.
Okay, Mom.
I'll walk Shikimori-san home.
You take care now.
Sorry about everything today, Shikimori-san.
I even fell asleep...
I enjoyed getting to see your sleeping face.
I don't sleep with my eyes open, do I?!
No need to worry.
What kinds of movies do you like, Izumi-san?
Hmm... I guess I like
stories about friendship.
Then why don't we see
something like that next time?
Sure!
When should we go again?
I think there's a new buddy film
coming out next month.
Let's go see it, then.
Okay!
SEE YOU~
Oh, I got a message.
From a friend?
No, it's from Motoko-san.
Motoko-san?!
Izumi Motoko
Why don't we go and learn
how to make meat and potato
stew together?
In a cooking class
Apparently, Shikimori-san really
has a way with older folks.
I'd love to!!